<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" ><generator uri="https://jekyllrb.com/" version="3.9.3">Jekyll</generator><link href="http://localhost:4000/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/atom+xml" /><link href="http://localhost:4000/" rel="alternate" type="text/html" /><updated>2024-02-16T10:11:44-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/feed.xml</id><title type="html">apouofm</title><entry><title type="html">Bylaws Committee</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/fraternity/bylaws/2024/02/16/bylaws-committee.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Bylaws Committee" /><published>2024-02-16T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-02-16T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/fraternity/bylaws/2024/02/16/bylaws-committee</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/fraternity/bylaws/2024/02/16/bylaws-committee.html">&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce the formation of a Bylaws Committee to rewrite our fraternity chapter’s bylaws. This committee will be responsible for reviewing and updating our current bylaws to ensure they align with our chapter’s values and goals.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The committee will consist of dedicated members who are passionate about shaping the future of our fraternity. They will work collaboratively to draft, revise, and finalize the new set of bylaws.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;If you are interested in joining the Bylaws Committee or have any suggestions or ideas, please reach out to &lt;a href=&quot;mailto:egeiss@umich.edu&quot;&gt;egeiss@umich.edu&lt;/a&gt;. We value your input and look forward to your participation.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Stay tuned for updates on the committee’s progress and important dates related to the bylaws revision process. Together, we can create a stronger and more inclusive fraternity chapter.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Thank you for your support!&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><category term="Fraternity" /><category term="Bylaws" /><summary type="html">We are excited to announce the formation of a Bylaws Committee to rewrite our fraternity chapter’s bylaws. This committee will be responsible for reviewing and updating our current bylaws to ensure they align with our chapter’s values and goals.</summary></entry><entry><title type="html">Welcome to the New Pledges!</title><link href="http://localhost:4000/2024/01/21/welcome-new-pledges.html" rel="alternate" type="text/html" title="Welcome to the New Pledges!" /><published>2024-01-21T00:00:00-05:00</published><updated>2024-01-21T00:00:00-05:00</updated><id>http://localhost:4000/2024/01/21/welcome-new-pledges</id><content type="html" xml:base="http://localhost:4000/2024/01/21/welcome-new-pledges.html">&lt;p&gt;We are excited to announce that the rush period has officially come to an end. We want to extend a warm welcome to all the new pledges who have joined our organization. We are thrilled to have you on board and look forward to an amazing journey together.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;embracing-new-beginnings&quot;&gt;Embracing New Beginnings&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;As we embark on this new chapter, we encourage all the new pledges to embrace the opportunities and challenges that lie ahead. This is a time for growth, learning, and building lifelong friendships. We believe that each and every one of you has the potential to make a positive impact within our community.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;h2 id=&quot;getting-started&quot;&gt;Getting Started&lt;/h2&gt;

&lt;p&gt;To get started, please familiarize yourself with our organization’s values, mission, and guidelines. We have a series of exciting events and activities planned to help you integrate into our community and get to know your fellow pledges. Stay tuned for more information and updates.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Once again, welcome to the family! Let’s make this a memorable and rewarding experience for everyone.&lt;/p&gt;</content><author><name></name></author><summary type="html">We are excited to announce that the rush period has officially come to an end. We want to extend a warm welcome to all the new pledges who have joined our organization. We are thrilled to have you on board and look forward to an amazing journey together.</summary></entry></feed>